traviscu.org 2007-04-29

# Travis Credit Union - Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy is Important to Us**  
We value your Membership and your privacy is very important to us. Travis Credit Union respects your concerns about maintaining privacy of your personal information. We want to assure you that we maintain strict security procedures to protect your information.

We are committed to providing you with competitive products and services to meet your financial needs, which necessitates that we share information about you to complete your transactions and to provide you with certain financial opportunities. In order to do so, we have entered into agreements with nonaffiliated third party financial service providers and other companies that provide either services to us or additional financial products for you to consider. We may also disclose information about you under other circumstances as permitted or required by law. These disclosures typically include information to follow your instructions as you authorize, process transactions on your behalf, conduct our operations, or protect the security of our financial records.

It is the policy of Travis Credit Union not to sell any information to anyone or provide any member information to any list service for independent use.

**Information We Collect About You**  
To help us serve your financial needs, provide member service, offer new products and services and fulfill legal and regulatory requirements, we collect nonpublic personal information about you as follows:

  * Information you provide to us verbally or in writing on our membership application, loan applications, and other applications and forms, such as your name, address, Social Security Number, date of birth, assets, income and debt  

  * Information about your transactions with us, such as loan and share account histories and balances, payment history, ATM, and Credit and Check Card activity.  

  * Information we receive from consumer reporting agencies, such as your credit history or report and credit score.  

  * Passwords, Personal Identification Numbers, or other access codes created or that you create in connection with products or services we offer.  

  * Other sources, to verify the information you provide on applications, such as account and loan balances at other financial institutions as well as income and employment.

**Information We Disclose** _Disclosure to Nonaffiliated Third Parties_  
We may disclose non-public information in order to provide you with the products and services that you request or to effect, administer or enforce a transaction that you request or authorize. We may also disclose non-public personal information about you to the following types of non-affiliated third parties:

  * Financial service providers, such as ATM networks, mortgage insurers, escrow and title companies, bill payment processors, credit reporting agencies and similar consumer reporting agencies like ChexSystems  

  * Non-financial companies, such as check printers, data processors and businesses that prepare and distribute our account statements and marketing information  

  * Others, such as technical service consultants and Internet services companies.  

  * Non-public personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties as permitted or required by law

_Disclosure Under Marketing Arrangements_

We may also disclose information we collect (excluding your account numbers, PINs, passwords, other access codes, and Social Security Number) as described in “Information We Collect About You” above, to nonaffiliated third party companies that perform marketing and related services on our behalf, and to other financial service providers with whom we have joint marketing agreements, for the purpose of marketing and targeted direct mail solicitations of financial products and services that we believe may be of value and interest to you. In all instances, we only disclose the limited information necessary to perform these services and do not share information we have collected about you, except as permitted by law.

**If You Terminate Your Relationship With Us**  
If your credit union Membership is terminated we will not share information we have collected about you, except as permitted or required by law.

**Confidentiality and Security**  
To protect your privacy, we work only with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality protections and limit the use of information that we provide. All agreements with other companies, including joint marketing agreements, contain required confidentiality clauses that prohibit these companies from selling the information we provide to them to other third parties and require them to safeguard the information while in their possession.

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who have a specific business in utilizing your data. Our employees are trained in the importance of maintaining confidentiality and customer privacy. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations, California state laws and leading industry practices to safeguard your nonpublic personal information.

**Safeguarding Your Own Privacy**  
Each individual also has a responsibility to safeguard their financial information. 

Protect your account numbers, PINs and passwords. Never keep your PIN with your debit, ATM or credit card, which could provide access to your accounts if your card is lost or stolen. 

Use caution when disclosing your account numbers, Social Security numbers, etc. to other persons. If someone calls you, explains the call is on behalf of the credit union and asks for your account number, do not divulge that information. Official credit union staff will have access to your information and will not need to ask for it. 

Keep your information current. We need to have current information on how to reach you. If we detect or suspect possible fraudulent or unauthorized activity or use of an account, we need to be able to contact you. 

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, you may write the Privacy Officer at Travis Credit Union, P.O. Box 2069, Vacaville, CA 95696-2069 or call us at: (707) 449-4000 or (800) 877-8328

**Travis Credit Union  
P.O. Box 2069  
Vacaville, CA 95696

TCU-10020 (2007)

**
